Hello.
こんにちは
nice to meet you.
初めまして
May I know your name?
お名前を教えてもらっていいですか?
My name is Miya.
ミヤーです
Miya-chan.
ミヤーちゃん
Well, how old are you now?
えっと、今、歳いくつ?
I'm 20 years old now.
今、20歳です
20 years old?
20歳?
Yeah.
うん
Um, are you already working?
え っと、もう働いてるの?
I'm a student now.
今、学生です
Oh, I went to school.
あ、学校行ってんだ
So-so.
そこそこ
It looks kind of stylish.
なんかオシャレっぽいね
What series?
何系?
Ah, fashion-related.
あ、ファッション系の
Ah, right?
あ、でしょね
We have that kind of culture.
そういう文化やってます
Right?
でしょ
What, what are you going to do?
え、何するの?
Um, after you graduate from school, will you work at a sales office?
あの、学校卒業した後は販売所か?
That's right.
そうですよ
I think I'd like to live somewhere like that.
そっち系住みたいなと思ってます
I often do press work or design work.
よくよくはプレスやったりとか、デザインやったりとか
yes.
はい
Looks fashionable.
オ シャレっぽい
Do you know what you came here for today?
今日ここに何しに来たかは分かってます?
Eh, not really.
え、あんまり
Don't you understand much?
あんまり分かってない?
yes.
はい
I thought I'd mention it in a casual exchange earlier.
さっきなんか、軽くやりとりの中では伝えそうと思うけど
Somewhat.
若干
Somewhat?
若干?
That's what I had you come to today.
今日来てもらった、あれなんですけど
It's a leverage game.
イカセゲームです
Is it a leverage game?
イカセゲームですか?
If I had to choose between myself, would I lean towards S or M?
自分どっちかって言ったらS寄りとかM寄りとかあります?
Yeah, but I'll stop by the sun.
え、でも日に寄ります
Close to the sun.
日に寄る
It depends on my mood.
気分に寄ります
approach the other person.
相手に寄る
There is also that.
それもありますね
Depends on your mood.
気分に寄る
There are two patterns, one is that Bio-chan will talk about me within 10 minutes.
パターン2つあって、1個は ビオちゃんが10分以内に僕のこと
The one that challenges you to see if you can make it work.
を いかせられるか チャレンジするやつ
You can do whatever you want.
何してもいいです
It doesn't matter if you do it with your mouth or your hands,
別に なんか、口でしても手でしてもいいし なんだったら、
If you don't want to go, I can try something else, but no matter what.
行かねえんだったらもうなんか突っ込んでもいいけど 何しても
Okay, 10 minutes.
いい です、10分間
Let me go for now.
僕のことをとりあえずいかせる
The second challenge is that I will attack.
チャレンジのもう2つ目は 僕が攻めるんで、
If you don't go and endure it for 10 minutes, Bio-chan will be here.
10分間それに耐えてもらって 行かなかったら ビオちゃんがこ
Either way, if you succeed in the challenge, you will receive cash.
っち に で、どっちにしてもチャレンジ成功したら 現金で
I will give you 100,000 yen on the spot.
10万 円その場で渡します
amazing.
すごい
It's not an hourly wage, but a 10 minute break, which is amazing.
時給じゃなくて10分休憩で すごい
That's why I'm asking you to come today.
っていう感じで、今日来てもらっているんですけど どっちに
Do you?
します?
Well, don't say it, what should I do?
えー、 まぁ言うな、どうしよう
Which one is better?
どっちがいい?
What about the rejection department?
拒否部は?
I will attack.
攻めます
attack?
攻める?
yes.
はい
Shall we attack today?
今日は攻める?
feeling?
気分?
I will attack.
攻めます
How many people have experience with Whiplash?
むちげと経験人数何人くらいいるんですか?
Say, one hand?
言って 片手?
both hands?
両手?
I say it's one handed, but I'm using both hands, but I can fit it in.
片手って言いながら両手動いてるけど 収まるぐらいです
Enough to fit?
収まるぐらい?
I see.
そうか
copper?
どう?
I've been feeling pretty naughty for some time now.
結構なんか 今までなんか 普通にエッチな気分になって なんか
I'm at the stage where I'm reducing things before I jump in.
突 っ込む前のなんか 減らしたりとかしてる段階でさ 先に
Do you feel like you've let someone go?
なんか 行かせちゃった、みたいな あったりする?
there is.
あります
be.
ある
What kind of situation was that?
それはどういうシチュエンションだった?
By mouth.
口で
Are you thinking of letting me go first?
もうなんか、先に行かせようと思ったの?
Or did the other person leave on their own?
それとも相手が勝手に行っちゃった?
I went on my own.
勝手に行っちゃった
Did you leave on your own?
勝手に行っちゃった?
How long was that?
それ時間的にどんぐらいだった?
Yeah, but it was less than 10 minutes.
えー、でも10分以内だった
About 5 minutes.
5分とか
yes.
そう
Ah, yes.
あ、そう
I did it because of my strong enemy in the past.
強敵過去によってしたよ
I see.
そうか
5 minutes.
5分か
I wonder if I can do my best.
頑張れるかな
Eh, are you good at Pera?
え、ペラ得意?
Are you good at it?
得意かな?
I'm good at it.
得意です
good at?
得意?
But she has a cute face, so I guess it's normal.
でも、 顔かわいいから、普通になんか そう
By the way, there is a punishment game for this,
ちなみにこれさ、罰ゲーム一応があって、
If I could get there in 10 minutes, I would have paid 100,000 yen.
10分で行かせられると全然10万円お支払いしてるんですけど、
Of course, it's a part-time job at a public school, so there are punishment games,
もちろん公学バイトなんで、 罰ゲームもあって、
When I messed up, I turned on the video and had them remove that much of it.
失敗した時、 ビデオ回してまんまでそんなにハミ取りさせてもら
There was a punishment game called Eru.
える という罰ゲームがあったんですけど、
It's a punishment game.
罰ゲームですね
How about that?
そこどう?
it's okay.
大丈夫です
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
If you lose, you'll just be like that chimp who was talking all along.
負けたら、 普通にあの、逆になんか今まで喋ってたチンプ、
It's like you're being pushed straight into it,
そのまま突っ込まれるかたちになるんですけど、
Does it look okay?
大丈夫そうですか?
Well, I'll put it in the big finisher,
あの、フィニッシャーの大きいなかに出しますけど、
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
So, as a challenge, even if you take advantage of me in 10 minutes,
じゃあ、 チャレンジ的には、 10分間で僕のことを活かしても
Yes, yes.
ら うっていう、 はい
I will do my best in this challenge.
チャレンジで、 頑張ります
There are also punishment games.
罰ゲームもありで
yes.
はい
OK?
大丈夫ですか?
yes.
はい
Well then, let's do our best.
じゃあ、頑張ろうか
please.
お願いします
Finisher!
フィニッシャー!
Are you ready?
準備となりました?
yes.
はい
Shall we go ahead? Well then.
やって いきますか、じゃあ
Well then, could you please let me know if it's okay for me to take on the challenge?
じゃあ、チャレンジするのに、 いいのか教えてもらっていい
Is it?
ですか?
Well, let me subtract 100,000 yen, which I can afford.
えー、 引かせて、 10万円、 余裕だ
I'll use it.
使います
Can you afford it?
余裕で?
I can afford it.
余裕で
Well then, shall we go?
じゃあ、 いきますか
In 10 minutes.
10分で
yes.
はい
Yo.
よー
vinegar
ス
Tart.
ター ト
It's really beautiful.
なんかめっちゃ綺麗だね
It's true.
本当だよ
Yeah.
うん
With sea cut.
シ ーカットで
Slender.
スレンダー
Yeah.
うん
I talk to you a lot, but please cut out my time by another 10 minutes.
俺、結構話しかけていくけどさ、 時間をもう10分カットして
Cut it.
カットして
Can I take this off?
これ、脱がせていいの?
Okay, okay.
いいよ、いいよ
If you can watch it for 10 minutes, you've already won.
10分間見かせられれば、もう勝ちなんだね
It's good to do this.
これ、したっていいっすよ
A lot of air comes out.
大気めっちゃ出る
Yeah.
うん
Eh, 80%.
えー、80%
It's been a little over 5 minutes, are you okay?
ちょっと5分経ったけど大丈夫?
Are you okay.
大丈夫
Seriously.
本気で
100% serious.
本気の100%
That's it.
そんなで
It's over.
終了です
It's finished.
終 了です
It was no good.
ダメだったー
30%, 80% this.
30%、80%これ
Finally full power.
最後はもうフルパワー
Yes, it was at full power.
うん、フルパワーだったけど
Full power, no good.
フルパワー、ダメだった
That's strange.
おかしいね
It used to take 5 minutes.
今までだったら5分でした
Is it different from before?
今までと違った?
It's tough.
てごわい
I really understood.
てごわかった
It's already been 10 minutes, but...
もうこっちだってさ、なんて10分いっちゃったけど、
It's been 10 and a half minutes each time.
毎回10分半になってくる
Yeah, definitely.
うん、確かに
Every time, I train to stop when I'm about to go.
毎回、いきそうに止める訓練してる
By the way, just to confirm,
ちなみに、一応確認なんですけど、
Nee-chan, you got out.
ねえちゃん、抜けたの
sex.
セ ックス
I probably went there because they were doing some repairs while I was there.
しながら修理とかするから、俺多分そこ行ったんだよ
Yeah, I see.
うん、なるほど
Eh, which one?
えー、どっちだろう
Free.
フリー
Hermey above.
上のハーメイ
This is it.
これだ
Let's touch on it today.
今日そもそも触ろうね
This time, I don't have to rush, so I'll be fair.
今回、急ぎじゃなくていいから、ちょっとフェアして
Just like before, all about the nipples.
さっきのありあえず、ちょっと乳首すべて
Don't do it once upon a time.
昔々やんないで
It might have been faster if this was done slowly.
これゆっくりやられてるほうが速攻でいったかも
I was a little disappointed in the prize money, but what was it like?
ちょっと賞金は残念でしたけど、 どうでした?
it was fun.
楽しかった
楽 しかった
I feel like I'm having fun and feeling better just by looking at the results.
結果ぐらいでも楽しく気持ちよくなったっていう感じ
What is the level of this cock?
このチンポはレベル的に、レベルどんぐらい?
10 levels.
レベル10段階
8?
Was there a stronger one?
もっと強いのいた?
secret.
秘密
Was there an amazing one?
すごいのいた?
But I'm sure.
だが、きっと
About 8 levels is just right.
8段階ぐらいがちょうどいい
Next time, if another big game project comes out,
ちょっと次、また高額ゲーム企画出たら、
Please contact me for the final match.
一応ご連絡して、 最終戦
Thank you for your hard work today.
今日もお疲れさまでした
thank you.
ありがとうございます